[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to the Option Gyan channel.
Friends, today we are going to discuss this
topic. Its name is HCL. You have to
click on the current date, that is,
you have to like around 111.
Friends, the stock had its breakout
two days ago.
Now, it is expected that it will go towards its new high.
Friends, it also
hit around 120. So, we hope that it will
break 120 very soon. So,
you have to bike the current high around 111.
As the market is at a lifetime
high, if it goes down, friends,
you have to buy it around 99.
And finally, you have to do it around 74. So
friends, now you have to
invest only 30% of your capital in some stocks. That is, in
111 pack, you will invest only 30% of your capital. The
remaining 30% of your capital will be invested
around 99.
And the final 40% of your capital will be invested
at 124.  So
friends, if it gives closing below this for two-three days then you will exit from this position.
Hello friends, I am
telling you the method of doing ABS in the stock
and I always give this exit point.
You people see this moving very far away.
How would you feel about it, but friends, I am
not talking about investing your capital all at once in the market. Friends,
if you people invest the entire stock in the pursuit of making money very quickly, then it is
possible that you may get a good profit,
but if you ever get stuck in any stock, then you will
not be able to keep it for long because
all your money is paid to the stock and
when the stock goes down, friends, at that
time whatever you think is not working, you get
carried away by your emotions
and finally we have to bear the loss, so
when we will do it in a way that
where to invest, where to invest,
how to consolidate, then we will know first, we will
first be mentally prepared so that the show can
continue, even if it comes to 0-4, then
we will invest capital accordingly, then we
Friends will definitely benefit in the long term.
I had placed a stop on August 8,
friends. Last time, that
time it goes around 558
and the juice around the stomach and then I
told him that it has to be done among you people at 472
and if it goes below 443, then
you people should unite. Now, if that
stock goes around 450, friends, and the same
information is hit in the passbook and today the stock
comes out around 540,
if someone has to back 558 and it also happens at 472,
etc., then its average will
come around 515, friends. And if you
take a stop loss and fold a part of 540, it will go
up, but
still let me tell you that as of today,
after one month, you are getting a
profit of almost 5 percent, that
in a month, friends,
if you invest money in FD for the whole year, then you
get 67 percent, here you get
5 percent in a month, so you
can understand that  How do we increase the
stop, whatever breakfast pain happens and
now the record is made again, then where to
go and wish, then the
line which I gave you guys, so
see, I could not break it, so
all these things have to be explained that if it
goes below this, then it is possible that the chart may become negative, if it becomes
negative then we exit
and then it will become positive tomorrow,
after this our stock
can deceive us and go up, so
all this is part of the game, friends, this is
in the market, so we have to learn and
then earn, sometimes we will
not earn money like this, sometimes we also have to learn in cars,
yes, if someone's
grave is given in the market, then all these things
which are at life time high in the market,
so we always have to keep in mind that
where will the stock go down, then where to
Everest from there, all these things should be
in your mind, on this topic friends, the
fundamentals are also strong, that too I will
discuss with you, so
I have told you guys the levels, where to wish
and where  We have to wish where to
unite, let's discuss it fundamentally
that this token friends, if you click on this topic, if
needed then this
window opens, here you have to go to fundamentals, you will
click on its details, it will
take you to that
if we talk about the financial trend of the company, then
you will see an increase,
if we
talk about sector-21 of 2018, then it has
increased its revenue by almost 22% and if we
talk about the non-profit of the company, then also it has
increased its profit by 90% in 2018,
if we talk about the financial statement, then all the
three points are visible to you here
that the daily revenue growth of the company is
more than 15-25 times that of the industry,
where the revenue growth of the industry is 3.0
percent, whereas the revenue growth of this company is
around 60%, friends the company has
increased its almost in 5 years.  It is going to be
tense
and if we talk about the net income of the company,
friends, then that too is more than the net income of the industry,
where the net interest margin of the industry is
11.12%, there the net interest margin of this company is
9060, so you must be thinking that I
refer to the system,
you people have the fundamental view of the company,
so now you can understand whether to consider it or
not,
I hope you liked my video
and it will be very beneficial for you,
with this hope friends I end my video,
thank you,
so friends, if you liked this video, then
please do not forget to like, share and subscribe,
thank you for watching my video
[Music]